<idea-plugin version="2">
    <id>pw.mcclure.djaneiro.pycharm</id>
    <name>Djaneiro for PyCharm</name>
    <version>1.2</version>
    <vendor email="jetbrains@mcclure.pw" url="https://www.mcclure.pw">Brian McClure</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
      <p>This was originally a pure port of the Djaneiro plugin for Sublime Text,
      but new features have been added not found in the original plugin.</p>
      <p>It's a collection of live templates for common patterns encountered
      when building Django applications (with a couple generic python uses) specifically
    useful for models, forms, widgets, views, and templates.

    <p>For example, the following expansions for models and forms can be made:
    </p>

    <pre><code>
    mchar&lt;TAB--> $FIELDNAME$ = models.CharField($name$ , max_length=50)$END$
    fchar&lt;TAB--> $FIELDNAME$ = forms.CharField($ARGS$)$END$
    </code></pre>

    <p>Where each variable between dollar signs($) (e.g., $FIELDNAME$, $NAME$, etc)
    is a stopping point for the cursor each time enter is pressed.</p>

    <p> The abbreviations generally adhere to the following conventions:

    <ul>
        <li>Model field templates are prefixed by 'm' with the exception of `fk`,
        `m2m`, and `o2o` fields</li>
        <li>Form field templates are prefixed by 'f'</li>
        <li>Widgets are prefixed by 'w'</li>
        <li>Settings are prefixed by 's'</li>
        <li>Template templates have no prefix, nor do generic python templates</li>
    </ul>

    </p>

    <p>
    For a full listing of the abbreviations, see the github repo:
    <a href='https://github.com/brmc/pycharm-djaneiro/tree/master/docs'>
    https://github.com/brmc/pycharm-djaneiro/tree/master/docs</a>
    </p>

    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
    v1.2 -
    <ul>
        <li>Added live templates for django settings</li>
        <li>Migrated to python 3.6 with no plans for backwards compatibility</li>
        <li>fixed bug in postgres fields. they no longer expand to one giant variable</li>
        <li>removed duplication of `fip`</li>
    </ul>

    v1.1 -
    <ul>
        <li>Updated templates from upstream</li>
        <li>Included missing fields for models and forms</li>
        <li>Added Postgres model and form fields</li>
        <li>Added Widgets</li>
        <li>Added transpiler to convert between sublime text and jetbrains</li>
    </ul>
    v1.0 -
    <ul>
        <li>No changes since I originally commited to my github repo, which means there
        is no support for new fields added in the last 2 years.</li>
    </ul>
    ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <idea-version since-build="141.0"/>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <defaultLiveTemplatesProvider implementation="DjangoTemplateProvider"/>
    </extensions>

</idea-plugin>